ANTHONI PORTOCARRERO RODRIGUEZ

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PROFILE INFO

I am a 22-year-old student who is in the ninth cycle of the Software Engineering career. I define myself as an enthusiastic and applied person in what I do, I love and respect my career. I like to learn new technologies and development methods and I offer the best of me in each experience.

CONTACT

Phone

+51 958 920 823

Email

softwaretoni21@gmail.com

My Website

https://www.anthonidev.me

EDUCATION

2018 – in progress Software Engineer

UTP – Universidad tecnológica del Perú

2011 - 2016 secondary education

Fe y Alegría N° 43 La Salle

WORK EXPERIENCE

Huertas Inmobiliaria – System Operador 06-2021 09-2021

Provided solutions to the problems of the collaborators in the face of any inconvenience during the use of technological equipment (ICT), also perform automations with Python

Service Computer Technicians - Technical
03-2020 - 02-2021

We provide hardware repair services and software installations such as OS formatting, data backup and recovery.

I.E. Alexander Fleming -Computer Systems Assistant
12-2019 - 02-2020

Provided solutions to the problems of teachers in the face of any inconvenience during the use of technological equipment (ICT).

REFERENCE

Git hub

anthonidev

Web Site

anthonidev.me

SKILLS

Languages

Python SQL

JavaScript TypeScript

Frameworks and Libraries

React JS Tailwind

Next JS Django

Redux Framer Motion

Tools and Others

Git Postman

npm Terminal Linux